<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Hunge Labs</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Hunge Labs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:25:52 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hungelabs.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contributing</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/contributing/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:12:23 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/contributing/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 01:12:07 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/about/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Getting Started with Specialty Coffee - Pt. 1</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/intro/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:42:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/intro/</guid><description>A Quick Note Getting into specialty coffee can seem incredibly daunting at first glance. From seeing thousands of dollars of equipment online to nuanced (and at times, pretentious) flavor descriptors, specialty can appear as something of a walled garden.
This guide has been written with the express purpose of tearing down those walls. It does not assume any experience with coffee or sensory assessment, and aims to demystify the world of specialty in an approachable and friendly way.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Specialty Coffee - Pt. 2</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/what-is-coffee/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:42:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/what-is-coffee/</guid><description>Coffee - the plant In a strictly literal sense, brewing coffee is the steeping of a roasted seed harvested from a plant in the genus coffea. This genus contains several cultivated species, most commonly coffea arabica and coffea canephora, known as Arabica and Robusta respectively. Rarer are species such as stenophylla, liberica, and eugenioides, but coffea contains over 120 known species.
Historically, Robusta has been the staple of coffee consumption world-wide due to the higher yield, easier cultivation, and climate-tolerant genetics.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Specialty Coffee - Pt. 3</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/terms/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:42:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/terms/</guid><description>The Language of Specialty Flavor Descriptors The wold of specialty coffee is riddled with descriptors, from cocoa nibs to stone fruit to honeysuckle. These descriptors can&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Specialty Coffee - Pt. 4</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/properties/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 00:42:32 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/getting-started/properties/</guid><description>Words are important Coffee Roast Levels and Strength In the broader world, it is common to describe coffee roast levels (light, medium, dark, french, etc) with a &amp;ldquo;strength&amp;rdquo; value, associating darker roasts with stronger brews. However, the term strength is a misnomer - in the world of specialty coffee, strength refers to a measurable property of the brew unrelated to roast level.
Specifically, strength describes the concentration of coffee compounds in water.</description></item><item><title>A (rough) layout guide</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/meta/layout-guide/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 18:15:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/meta/layout-guide/</guid><description>I think it&amp;rsquo;d be good to document the way I&amp;rsquo;m planning on laying out the structure of the wiki going forward. As it stands, this is the layout of the wiki&amp;rsquo;s repo:
A bunch of dev files These generally are prefixed with an underscore (ex, &amp;ldquo;_data&amp;rdquo;) and for the most part, you don&amp;rsquo;t ever need to worry about that.
The actual wiki docs this is under the folder /wiki/ and is divided into</description></item><item><title>New Wiki, Who 'dis?</title><link>https://hungelabs.github.io/meta/welcome-to-the-wiki/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 May 2022 14:30:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://hungelabs.github.io/meta/welcome-to-the-wiki/</guid><description>Hi friends! This wiki is just getting started, but I think it&amp;rsquo;d be cool to lay out some ground work for where I (and the rest of the team) are trying to go.
As it stands, I have a couple goals I want to get done before I turn our contributors loose on the wiki.
Get our base pages and resources set. This would be all the nav links, contribution pages, any readme stuff, all the important shit.</description></item></channel></rss>